<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>culture on VRchina.cc</title>
    <link>https://vrchina.cc/categories/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in culture on VRchina.cc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 [VRchina.cc](https://vrchina.cc) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vrchina.cc/categories/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Characters of Chinese Cuisine</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/characters-of-chinese-cuisine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/characters-of-chinese-cuisine/</guid>
      <description>Chinese food culture is a precious part of Chinese culture. China is a vast country, taking up most of Asia and claiming much of its eastern coastline, which makes food in China vary from east to west, north to south.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Alcohol History and Culture</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/chinese-alcohol-history-and-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/chinese-alcohol-history-and-culture/</guid>
      <description>In China, alcohol is also called the &amp;ldquo;Water of History&amp;rdquo;, because the stories of alcohol can be traced back to almost every period in Chinese history. A legend says that Yi Di, the wife of the first Dynasty&amp;rsquo;s emperor Yu invented the method to make alcohol In ancient China, since alcohol was regarded as a sacred liquid, only when people made sacrificial offerings to the Heaven and the Earth or ancestors was it used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Food Therapy</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/chinese-food-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/chinese-food-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Chinese food therapy or nutrition therapy is an ancient practice in Traditional Chinese medicine that relies mainly on the consumption of natural food to heal the body. In Western countries, physicians generally regard dietary changes as an important part of medical treatment but not the primary cure to most diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Local Specialties</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/chinese-local-specialties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/chinese-local-specialties/</guid>
      <description>Local specialties in tourist cities of China have become a part of tourism. While enjoying sightseeing, visitors can also have a taste of all kinds of specialties in China. The following are some of the famous local specialties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hundred Schools of Thought</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/hundred-schools-of-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/hundred-schools-of-thought/</guid>
      <description>The Hundred Schools of Thought is the name given to philosophers and schools that flourished from 770 to 221 BC, an era of great cultural and intellectual expansion in China. Even though this period, known in its earlier part as the Spring and Autumn Period and the Warring States period in its latter part, was characterized by chaos and bloody battles, it is also known as the golden age of Chinese philosophy because a variety of thoughts and ideas were freely developed and discussed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laozi and the Daodejing</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/laozi-and-the-daodejing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/laozi-and-the-daodejing/</guid>
      <description>Laozi was a philosopher of ancient China and was a central figure in Taoism, also spelled &amp;ldquo;Daoism&amp;rdquo;. Laozi means &amp;ldquo;Old Master&amp;rdquo; and is generally considered an honorific Laozi is revered as a god in religious forms of Taoism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life of Confucius</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/life-of-confucius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/life-of-confucius/</guid>
      <description>Confucius has the greatest influence on Chinese characters. Besides being a great educationist, thinker, and unsuccessful politician, he was, first of all, an intellect with a noble morality. He pursued truth, kindness, and perfection throughout his life and his success and failure were largely due to his character, which had an everlasting impact on Chinese intellects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origin of Chinese Characters</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/4-language-and-literature/origin-of-chinese-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/4-language-and-literature/origin-of-chinese-characters/</guid>
      <description>As one of the most ancient characters, Chinese characters have played a significant role in the development of Chinese culture. Originally, ancient Sumerian and ancient Egyptian symbols existed, but only Chinese characters remain today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Mandarin</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/4-language-and-literature/standard-mandarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/4-language-and-literature/standard-mandarin/</guid>
      <description>Standard Mandarin, also known as Putonghua, which means &amp;ldquo;common speech&amp;rdquo;, is China&amp;rsquo;s official language. It is the language of education, government and law and almost all foreigners who study Chinese will learn this dialect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunzi and The Art of War</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/sunzi-and-the-art-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/sunzi-and-the-art-of-war/</guid>
      <description>Sunzi is the reputed author of &amp;ldquo;The Art of War&amp;rdquo;, which is considered the best single book ever written on the subject of war. Of Sunzi himself, little is known beyond his birth in the state of Qi and service to the emperor Helti of Wu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book of Changes</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/the-book-of-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/the-book-of-changes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Book of Changes&amp;rdquo;, or I Ching in Chinese, is unquestionably one of the most important works in the world. Its origin goes back to mythical antiquity, and it has occupied the attention of the most eminent scholars of China down to the present day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Five Key Flavors of Chinese Food</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/the-five-key-flavors-of-chinese-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/8-food-and-health/the-five-key-flavors-of-chinese-food/</guid>
      <description>Over China&amp;rsquo;s vast territory, the flavors of cuisine vary from one region to another, and usually one or two of the five flavors dominate. Flavor preferences can reflect features of geography, climate, agriculture, culture, and history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traditional Chinese Lantern Festival Held in the UK</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/5-education-and-communication/traditional-chinese-lantern-festival-held-in-the-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/5-education-and-communication/traditional-chinese-lantern-festival-held-in-the-uk/</guid>
      <description>Traditional Chinese Lantern Festival is an emerging project in the events of &amp;ldquo;Happy Chinese New Year&amp;rdquo; in the UK in recent years. Since 2014, it has been alive in the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>