<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>history on VRchina.cc</title>
    <link>https://vrchina.cc/tags/history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in history on VRchina.cc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 [VRchina.cc](https://vrchina.cc) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vrchina.cc/tags/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Terracotta Army</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/10-natural-and-cultural-wonders/the-terracotta-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/10-natural-and-cultural-wonders/the-terracotta-army/</guid>
      <description>The Terracotta Army is considered one of the greatest archaeological sites in the world, and one of the greatest discoveries of the 20th century. It is significant because the hundreds of detailed life-size models represent the army that triumphed over all other Chinese armies in the Warring States Period, and who ushered in the united imperial China era 2,200 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yungang Grottoes</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/10-natural-and-cultural-wonders/yungang-grottoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/10-natural-and-cultural-wonders/yungang-grottoes/</guid>
      <description>Yungang Grottoes represent the excellent achievement of Buddhist sculptural art of ancient China, and it is the largest among the four most famous ancient grotto complexes in China. Yungang Grottoes with 252 caves and 51,000 Buddhist statues are the classical masterpieces of Chinese Buddhist art in the 5th and 6th centuries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Jade Burial Suits</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/11-cultural-and-historical-relics/chinese-jade-burial-suits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/11-cultural-and-historical-relics/chinese-jade-burial-suits/</guid>
      <description>Just fifteen of the extraordinary head-to-toe jade suits that promised immortality to the Chinese imperial family have ever been found. The ancient Chinese believe that when a person dies, he or she will enter into the afterlife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classification of Chinese Poetry</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/4-language-and-literature/classification-of-chinese-poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/4-language-and-literature/classification-of-chinese-poetry/</guid>
      <description>The development of Chinese poetry can be divided into three main periods: the early period, characterized by folk songs in simple, repetitive forms; the classical period from the Han Dynasty to the fall of the Qing Dynasty, in which several different forms were developed; and the modem period of westernized free verse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education in Ancient China</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/5-education-and-communication/education-in-ancient-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/5-education-and-communication/education-in-ancient-china/</guid>
      <description>A good education has always been highly valued in China. As far back as the Shang Dynasty, inscriptions on bones or tortoise shells were the simple records of teaching and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heshi Jade</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/11-cultural-and-historical-relics/heshi-jade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/11-cultural-and-historical-relics/heshi-jade/</guid>
      <description>From Neolithic times, the Chinese have been extremely fond of jade and have made this magical stone an inseparable part of Chinese culture and art.
In China the national passion for jade gave that stone much the same superiority that lapis lazuli had in Sumer and the Chinese saying &amp;ldquo;Gold has a value; jade is invaluable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hundred Schools of Thought</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/hundred-schools-of-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/hundred-schools-of-thought/</guid>
      <description>The Hundred Schools of Thought is the name given to philosophers and schools that flourished from 770 to 221 BC, an era of great cultural and intellectual expansion in China. Even though this period, known in its earlier part as the Spring and Autumn Period and the Warring States period in its latter part, was characterized by chaos and bloody battles, it is also known as the golden age of Chinese philosophy because a variety of thoughts and ideas were freely developed and discussed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Dedicated Scientist and Agricultural Advancement</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/3-scientific-development-and-invention/one-dedicated-scientist-and-agricultural-advancement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/3-scientific-development-and-invention/one-dedicated-scientist-and-agricultural-advancement/</guid>
      <description>Yuan Longping was awarded 5-million-yuan State Supreme Science and Technology Prize for his high yield hybrid rice species in 2001 and 2013. This award is viewed as a &amp;ldquo;Chinese Nobel Prize&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origin of Chinese Characters</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/4-language-and-literature/origin-of-chinese-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/4-language-and-literature/origin-of-chinese-characters/</guid>
      <description>As one of the most ancient characters, Chinese characters have played a significant role in the development of Chinese culture. Originally, ancient Sumerian and ancient Egyptian symbols existed, but only Chinese characters remain today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Festival</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/spring-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/spring-festival/</guid>
      <description>The first day of the first lunar month is regarded as the New Year of the Chinese- the Spring Festival. It is the most important and ceremonious traditional festival in China, just like Christmas Day to the Westerners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunzi and The Art of War</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/sunzi-and-the-art-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/2-philosophy-and-wisdom/sunzi-and-the-art-of-war/</guid>
      <description>Sunzi is the reputed author of &amp;ldquo;The Art of War&amp;rdquo;, which is considered the best single book ever written on the subject of war. Of Sunzi himself, little is known beyond his birth in the state of Qi and service to the emperor Helti of Wu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Belt and Road</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/5-education-and-communication/the-belt-and-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/5-education-and-communication/the-belt-and-road/</guid>
      <description>Complex and profound changes are taking place in the world. When Chinese President Xi Jinping visited Central Asia and Southeast Asia in September and October of 2013, he raised the initiative of jointly building the Silk Road Economic Belt and the 21 st_Century Maritime Silk Road, which have attracted close attention from all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dragon Boat Festival</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-dragon-boat-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-dragon-boat-festival/</guid>
      <description>Falling on the fifth day of the fifth month according to the Chinese lunar calendar, the Dragon Boat Festival is one of the greatest significant occasions among all the festivals widely celebrated in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ever Shining Four Great Inventions of Ancient China</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/3-scientific-development-and-invention/the-ever-shining-four-great-inventions-of-ancient-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/3-scientific-development-and-invention/the-ever-shining-four-great-inventions-of-ancient-china/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s long history has seen some extremely important inventions emerge, most noticeably gunpowder, paper making, printing and the compass, which, in the words of Roger Bacon, changed the whole appearance and status of things in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Origin of the Double-Seventh Day</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-origin-of-the-double-seventh-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-origin-of-the-double-seventh-day/</guid>
      <description>Legend has it that every year on the night of the Double-Seventh Day, the Weaving Girl in heaven and the Cowherd would meet at the Magpie Bridge. The Weaving Girl is a beautiful and smart fairy with deft hands and the women in the mortal world will beg for intelligence and deft needlework from her; hence July 7 of the lunar calendar is also called Begging-for-Dexterity FestivaL Therefore, the Double-Seventh Day is more than a Chinese Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silk Road Dream of China&#39;s High-speed Trains</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/3-scientific-development-and-invention/the-silk-road-dream-of-chinas-high-speed-trains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/3-scientific-development-and-invention/the-silk-road-dream-of-chinas-high-speed-trains/</guid>
      <description>Generally speaking, a rail network that offers 200-350 km/h trains is an HSR (High-Speed Railway) network in China. High-speed trains were once the preserve of Japan, with its &amp;ldquo;bullet train&amp;rdquo;, and France, with its TG~.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tomb Sweeping Day</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-tomb-sweeping-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-tomb-sweeping-day/</guid>
      <description>The Tomb Sweeping Day also called &amp;ldquo;Qing Ming&amp;rdquo; in Chinese has been a traditional Chinese practice for over 2,500 years and falls on the 15th day of the Spring Equinox, which usually falls on the 4th or 5th of April.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water-Splashing Festival of the Dai People</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/water-splashing-festival-of-the-dai-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/water-splashing-festival-of-the-dai-people/</guid>
      <description>Water-Splashing Festival is the most ceremonious traditional festival of the Dai minority group. It usually takes place in mid-April of the solar calendar, often ten days before or after the Tomb-sweeping Day, and lasts three to seven days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>