<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>food on VRchina.cc</title>
    <link>https://vrchina.cc/tags/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in food on VRchina.cc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 [VRchina.cc](https://vrchina.cc) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vrchina.cc/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Characters of Chinese Cuisine</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/characters-of-chinese-cuisine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/characters-of-chinese-cuisine/</guid>
      <description>Chinese food culture is a precious part of Chinese culture. China is a vast country, taking up most of Asia and claiming much of its eastern coastline, which makes food in China vary from east to west, north to south.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Alcohol History and Culture</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/chinese-alcohol-history-and-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/chinese-alcohol-history-and-culture/</guid>
      <description>In China, alcohol is also called the &amp;ldquo;Water of History&amp;rdquo;, because the stories of alcohol can be traced back to almost every period in Chinese history. A legend says that Yi Di, the wife of the first Dynasty&amp;rsquo;s emperor Yu invented the method to make alcohol In ancient China, since alcohol was regarded as a sacred liquid, only when people made sacrificial offerings to the Heaven and the Earth or ancestors was it used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Food Therapy</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/chinese-food-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/chinese-food-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Chinese food therapy or nutrition therapy is an ancient practice in Traditional Chinese medicine that relies mainly on the consumption of natural food to heal the body. In Western countries, physicians generally regard dietary changes as an important part of medical treatment but not the primary cure to most diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Shadow Puppetry</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/9-arts-and-crafts/chinese-shadow-puppetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/9-arts-and-crafts/chinese-shadow-puppetry/</guid>
      <description>Shadow puppetry, also known as shadow play, is one of China&amp;rsquo;s historic folk arts. Performed by three to five puppeteers, shadow puppetry is a form of storytelling that uses puppets against an illuminated backdrop to create the illusion of movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Local Specialties</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/chinese-local-specialties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/chinese-local-specialties/</guid>
      <description>Local specialties in tourist cities of China have become a part of tourism. While enjoying sightseeing, visitors can also have a taste of all kinds of specialties in China. The following are some of the famous local specialties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dragon Boat Festival</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-dragon-boat-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-dragon-boat-festival/</guid>
      <description>Falling on the fifth day of the fifth month according to the Chinese lunar calendar, the Dragon Boat Festival is one of the greatest significant occasions among all the festivals widely celebrated in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Five Key Flavors of Chinese Food</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/the-five-key-flavors-of-chinese-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/8-food-and-health/the-five-key-flavors-of-chinese-food/</guid>
      <description>Over China&amp;rsquo;s vast territory, the flavors of cuisine vary from one region to another, and usually one or two of the five flavors dominate. Flavor preferences can reflect features of geography, climate, agriculture, culture, and history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Origin of the Double-Seventh Day</title>
      <link>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-origin-of-the-double-seventh-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrchina.cc/blog/sketch/7-festivals-and-celebrations/the-origin-of-the-double-seventh-day/</guid>
      <description>Legend has it that every year on the night of the Double-Seventh Day, the Weaving Girl in heaven and the Cowherd would meet at the Magpie Bridge. The Weaving Girl is a beautiful and smart fairy with deft hands and the women in the mortal world will beg for intelligence and deft needlework from her; hence July 7 of the lunar calendar is also called Begging-for-Dexterity FestivaL Therefore, the Double-Seventh Day is more than a Chinese Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>